Is that actually "love"?
But isn't this "experiment"
to figure that out?
B-But...
Now, now. Let's just chill
and take it easy, yeah?
Oh, right. I have something you'll like.
Here.
I mean, you haven't even
said, "I like you" yet!
Whoa!
Huh?
Her face just now...
was priceless.
It's probably because of...
yesterday's date.
No, was it the nurse's office?
No, before then.
Why...
We often know ourselves the least.
It's almost like...
I want Senpai to fall in love with me.
Choco Anpan
Is this yours, Ichi?
You don't usually carry
sweets around, do you?
Nah.
What? Is it for the Prince?
Yeah. But I don't need it anymore.
It really isn't like you.
To think Ichi was going to
give something this cute.
I asked you this before...
but why are you so into her?
Her face?
I was the dumbass for asking.
I don't know why,
but I always want to look at her.
And when I do, I can't
stop looking at her.
But I don't know why.
I think even if Yoi-chan were a man,
I would feel the same way.
C'mon, man!
Uh, what do you call it?
I'm like a Yoi-chan enthusiast,
or a fanatic or something.
Y'know, I've been thinking about it.
Isn't that what people
call love at first sight?
And an intense case, at that.
Huh?!
Oh, is that not it?
I always thought that's what it was.
Because if you can't
keep your eyes off her,
it's gotta be love.
Love.
Huh? Seriously? What part?
Am I really gushing to you
guys all the time?
More like leaving us on read. And unread.
And generally ignoring us.
What I'm saying is,
the way you're treating her is totally
different from the girls you've dated.
So I thought this time you
might seriously be in love, Ichi.
Huh? Seriously in love?
How can you tell?
I mean, even I don't
know that much about it.
You could probably figure it out
if you gave it a little thought.
What kind of clueless Prince are you?
I mean, you haven't even
said, "I like you" yet!
Why did I say that?!
I want to find a hole and crawl into it!
I wonder what Senpai
thought when I said it.
It's not like that's even what I
wanted to say.
Why can't I ever be honest?
I could have said something
a little cuter.
I mean, because I'm a girl, of course!
No deeper meaning behind it than that!
Tomorrow, when I see him,
I'll properly apologize.
Yoi-chan, let's go buy some juice!
I'm so sleepy.
H-How strange...
He hasn't randomly showed up!
Yoi-chan...
What's going on?
Hey, wasn't expecting you to be here.
Ichi in the classroom during lunch.
Hey, wanna shoot some hoops?
We'll cheer you on.
You're really good at
basketball, aren't you?
Oh, for real?
But my leg has been acting
up since yesterday.
Huh? Are you okay?
Hey, Ichimura!
There's a first-year here for you...
Huh? The Prince?
What about his leg?
Yoi-chan!
What's up?
What's goin' on?
Uh, well, um...
I just...
What's this?
Really?
Can it be?
Aren't they always together?
This way.
So? What did you want to see me for?
I thought you might be feeling bothered
about what I said yesterday.
Oh.
Nah, I'm not bothered at all.
Is that... so?
That's strange.
Why did that hit me so hard?
Hey, what do you wanna do about gyoza?
Gyoza? You mean from the other day?
Yeah. We weren't able to go, yeah?
I've been craving gyoza ever since.
I know that feeling.
Right?!
So, I figured we could go somewhere close.
You mean... you and me?
Uh, Who else is here?
Gy...
Gyoza.
I-I want to go!
Then how about today? Are you free?
Oh, only after work.
I need to help with prep,
so I should be done by 7PM.
Okay. I'll hit you up later.
Ah, no way, I'm so happy.
About the gyoza, of course!
Seriously, what is this emotional
rollercoaster I'm on?
Chinese Cuisine
Welcome! How many in your party?
Oh, for two please.
Wow, there's a lot.
Hey, this one's good.
I know it's a bit late to say it,
but I don't come to places
like this very often,
so I'm a bit nervous.
Oh, really?
You seem like you're used to it, Senpai.
Hmm? Yeah, I can't cook at all, so.
Don't even know how to boil rice.
Oh, right.
Didn't he say he was
living on his own before?
I wonder if I'm allowed
to ask him about that...
Um...
Hey, it's Ichi!
Ugh. The loud ones are here.
What's this? What's this?!
Getting dinner together?!
I'm so jealous!
Ah, and the yelling starts.
Harsh, man.
Hey, can we join ya?
I wanted a chance to really
talk to the Prince for once.
No can do.
Could you leave us alone?
Look at him, treating us like
we're a third wheel...
Kuwa, could you take
Sentaro away somewhere?
You got it.
Wha? Aw, c'mon!
I've thought this before,
but this guy can just say things
like that at the drop of a hat.
I'm sure I'm the only one
who keeps getting flustered.
Oh, yeah.
Hey, Prince!
Sorry for eating your Choco anpan!
Kuwa, you little...
Those guys are gonna pay for this later.
Thank you for waiting.
Wow, it looks delicious!
Man, I'm starving.
Oh, Yoi-chan, chili oil?
Th-Thank you very... much.
They're totally watching me.
Sorry, Yoi-chan.
Could you scootch over?
Stop looking at her, dumbass.
Whoa, seriously?!
He's really done it!
He's so...
close...
Sorry, it's a little
tight, but bear with me.
How am I supposed to eat gyoza like—
Is it too cramped? You good?
I'm fine. I'm a little nervous, but...
Oh, what was I about to say?
Well, you know, I'm not used to
being close to a man like this!
I'm sure this is nothing
to you, Senpai, but...
Ah, I just dug my own grave.
I'm nervous.
Right now, I'm nervous.
There you go again,
saying stuff like that.
I'm not going to be fooled.
Oh gosh...
My heart...
Hey, over there.
There's two boys sitting close together.
Are they flirting? So cute!
Right?!
It's going to get cold if we don't eat it.
It burns...
The gyoza was good, yeah?
How about we go to a different
one next time?
Oh, sure...
Let's do that.
Man, I wasn't expecting
to see those two there.
I can't remember what it tasted like.
That joint is popular, so I
see familiar faces sometimes.
We gotta be extra careful next time.
Also, isn't Senpai acting normal?
Even after what he did to me...
Am I just being overly self-conscious?
Hey...
I've been thinking, in my own way,
about what you said yesterday.
Yeah...
Honestly, I still don't know.
I'm sorry.
Why did that hit me so hard again?
So, can I try something out?
Are you sure?
I'm really gonna do it if we
stay like this any longer.
W-Wait a min—
Oh, wait, I can't.
I was just eating gyoza.
Does my breath stink?
You good?
I-I'm fine.
That was a close one.
Never mind that, though!
What was I about to...?
Oh, hey, you want some gum?
They gave it to us at the restaurant.
Thank you.
What timing.
So.
Personally, I don't wanna destroy
the thing we've had going.
What do you think?
Would it be all right if I held your hand?
Wh-What are you talking about?!
We said at the start that we weren't
going to do stuff like that!
But it seemed like you were okay
with the kiss just now.
I-I just froze in place because
you caught me off guard!
Besides, it's strange to offer your hand
to see if you like someone or not!
It should be the other way around!
It's just...
I've never experienced a platonic
relationship like this before.
I need to try a bunch of tests
to figure out how I feel.
P-Platonic?!
Here.
If you don't want to, I won't.
But people might mistake
us for two guys again.
I couldn't care less about that.
We ended up holding hands anyway.
Senpai's hand is hot.
That was unexpected...
Is his the only hand that's hot?
Yoi! Are you done in there?
I couldn't stand him at first.
But before I knew it,
I was fine with him.
He's not a bad person, and it's not
that I don't like him... maybe...
I'm not even sure of my own feelings.
But I...
I find myself wanting Senpai
to really fall in love with me.
Not, "You're beautiful," or,
"I want you." Nothing like that.
If he just looked me in the
eye and said it to me, then...
Such a self-serving and
selfish way of thinking.
Oh, you're finally out!
Sis...
Sorry.
Senpai's still awake, isn't he?
By the way, did you hear?
It seems like we still haven't found
a new part-timer, and Dad was...
Should I message him about
something that happened today?
But what would I even say?
Yoi, you've got a boyfriend, don't you?
Oh, was I right?
N-No, we're not going out yet...
Oh? Not "yet," huh.
That's what I thought.
No wonder you're acting
differently than before.
Your expression just seems
a little more gentle...
Or maybe you've become
more emotionally expressive?
Come to think of it, Kotobuki and the
others said something similar to me.
More importantly,
what kind of person is he?
What's his name?
Do you have a picture?
Which celebrity does he look like?
We go to school together.
He's one year ahead of me.
And they call him the Prince.
What?!
There's someone besides you
with that strange nickname?!
Well, it's not exactly
fighting poison with poison.
But maybe someone more
prince-like than you
might actually be a better match for you.
That guy's got pretty good taste, I'd say.
All right, Imma take a
bath and head right to bed.
Gehehe
He's nothing like a prince, though.
I couldn't care less about that.
Well, that was... kinda... yeah.
Yoi Takiguichi
Good evening.
This is my first time messaging.
It's Takiguichi.
After thinking a little on what we
spoke about today, I would like to
propose the following:
How about a date next Saturday
or Sunday?
Got it.
At the time...
I couldn't go through with it.
'Cause I knew I wouldn't stop if I did.
I didn't get much sleep.
Oh, hey, Prince!
G-Good morning.
Thanks for yesterday.
I... can't properly look at him.
I have something I need to attend
to in the staff room, so...
Look at her go!
The Prince is fast on her feet, huh?
Real fast!
Hey, hey! Do you know
about the Gyoza Prince?
Prince? Not King?
Yeah, Prince!
Gotcha. Just kiddin'.
Huh? Um...
What kind of joke is this?
Well, it's just...
You're avoiding me again, aren't ya?
I'm not necessarily... avoiding you...
More like, there's no way I can
look at you in the eye
after what happened yesterday!
It's just...
You had a hair...
What did I just...
Did you think I was
going to try to kiss you again?
Relax. I won't do it again.
I told you, didn't I?
I won't do anything that you don't like.
Don't like?
Did I not like it?
Yesterday, too. And just now...
Really?
Well, I'm gonna head out.
Um...
I didn't necessarily...
I mean...
Yoi-chan?!
Huh? She said she was going to
wait for us in the courtyard.
Where did she go?
I'm sorry, I have to go.
Oh, there she is! Yoi-cha—
Huh? Hey, what's wrong?!
Are you feeling sick?
For a moment, I...
For a brief moment, I had my hopes
up somewhere deep within my heart.
All she did was hold
me back from going, and...
Whoa. What the heck?
My heart's out of control.
I feel like some kind of emotion
that the eye cannot see
is gradually changing me.
Temperature of Love
Translation:
Timing:
Editing:
Quality Control:
Final Quality Control:
Yukari Murase-Louden
Andy Ellis
Gabriella Alabanza
Salem Alabanza
Elizabeth Ellis
Nasu Oyaji Curry
Hiring Part-timer
Telephone number
Oh, I'm sorry to bother
you when you're so busy.
I called after seeing your flyer
for a part-time job.
Yes...
Yes.
It's Oji.
My name is Takuto Oji.